jidaw.com 2010-11-24

# JIDAW.COM: Privacy Policy

| 

**Privacy**

Thank you for visiting Jidaw.com and reviewing our privacy policy. Our Policy is to respect and protect the privacy of our users. This policy statement tells you how we collect information from you and how we use it. The information we receive depends upon what you do when visiting our site. 

**Your Email Address:**  
When you sign up for some of our services such as the IT Career Newsletter, Book contest, job link, you enter your email address and a variety of other personal information if you provide it to us in an E-mail or a request for information, on a registration form, or on a feedback or comment form on our site. Neither your email address nor any other information is ever made public to others by us. This information is used exclusively by us. 

We use this information to send e-mail and messages to our users on our content, about our company, and promotional material from our partners and/or advertisers.   
We will not disclose, sell or transfer any personal information to any third party unless required by law or authorized to do so by you. 

Any addition demographic information collected is used solely by us to gain a better understanding of who our audience is and to respond to your requests and to provide better services to you, our clients.. Should you send us an email, we may also use your email address to respond to your feedback. 

**Statistical Data:**  
For site management, we will collect and store non-personal information (i.e.: the name of domain from which you access the Internet; the date and time you access our site; the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site; and the information you view while visiting our web site) about your visit. This information is collected for statistical purposes. 

Our server collects this information for such purposes as assessing what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas. We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors. This information is only used by Jidaw.com and your specific data is never shared with others. 

**Third Party Advertising: data collection of non-personally identifying information:**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies,  [ click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

** Copyright**

All content included on this site is the property of Jidaw or its content suppliers. This site or any portion of this site may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited without the consent of Jidaw.

**How to contact us **  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us through the form on this page: <http://www.jidaw.com/contact.html>

**(FOR THE PURPOSES OF THIS POLICY JIDAW.COM INCLUDES AND REFERS TO JIDAW SYSTEMS LIMITED)**

_**Page Top**_

|  HOME |  ABOUT US |  COMMENTS |  CONTACT US |  BOOK SALES  
---|---|---|---|---  
HELP |  E-LEARNING |  CERTIFICATION |  TRAINING |  PREVIOUS JOBS  
  | PRIVACY | DISCLAIMER | [ SITEMAP](http://www.jidaw.com/sitemap.html) |    

****[Subscribe to the FREE IT Career Newsletter with valuable information bringing you practical, how-to tips and articles.](http://www.jidaw.com/subscareer.html)

[Subscribe to the FREE IT Career Newsletter with valuable information bringing you practical, how-to tips and articles.](http://www.jidaw.com/subscareer.html)
